<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Car Wash To Go</string>
    <string name="activitytitleregistro">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="nombre_completo">Full Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="edad">Age</string>
    <string name="telefono">Phone</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="password_Confirm">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="Terminos">By clicking Register, you agree to our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy and the use of cookies</string>
    <string name="verterminos">See terms</string>
    <string name="registrar">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="ya_tengo_user">I already have a user</string>
    <string name="ingresar">Log in</string>
    <string name="newuser">I don\'t have a user</string>
    <string name="olvidepassword">Did you forget your password?</string>
    <string name="perfil">Profile</string>
    <string name="chat">Chat list</string>
    <string name="buscarcwman">Search Car Wash Man</string>
    <string name="buscarautos">Search Car</string>
    <string name="working">Working</string>
    <string name="autolavado">Auto wash finished!</string>
    <string name="locationwash">Washing location</string>
    <string name="llamara">Call to:</string>
    <string name="llamara2">Are you sure you want to dial the user?</string>
    <string name="permisoubicacion">Accept location permissions</string>
    <string name="permisoubicacion2">Accept location permissions</string>
    <string name="permisogps">Grant GPS permission</string>
    <string name="online">Online</string>
    <string name="escrbe">Write something..</string>
    <string name="escrbiendo">Typing..</string>
    <string name="lastm">Last Message</string>
    <string name="newm">New Message</string>
    <string name="lastconcetion">Last connection</string>
    <string name="llenaresnaje">Fill to send message ..</string>
    <string name="borrar">Delete</string>
    <string name="eliminarmsg">Delete Message</string>
    <string name="msgeliminado">Deleted message</string>
    <string name="onlyyoumsg">You can only delete your messages</string>
    <string name="hismssg">His Message</string>
    <string name="delivered">Sent</string>
    <string name="tpago">Paypal payment method</string>
    <string name="fecha">Date</string>
    <string name="pagar">Pay</string>
    <string name="pagado">Paid via Paypal</string>
    <string name="catpagar">Enter amount to pay</string>
    <string name="icant">Enter amount to pay</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="lavar">To wash</string>
    <string name="chats">Chats</string>
    <string name="contranocoinci">Passwords don\'t match</string>
    <string name="min5">Minimum 5 characters</string>
    <string name="veremailenviada">Email Verification Sent</string>
    <string name="error">Error! Email not sent</string>
    <string name="pasosolvidepass">Enter your email to receive a reset password link</string>
    <string name="ingresocompletado">Login Completed!</string>
    <string name="si">Yes</string>
    <string name="linkreset">Reset password link has been sent to your email</string>
    <string name="errorlinkreset">Error! The reset link has not been sent</string>
    <string name="errorcredenciales">Error with credentials entered!</string>
    <string name="nofound">No results found</string>
    <string name="lavaraqui">Wash Here</string>
    <string name="obteniedocarwashman">Getting your Car Wash Man ..</string>
    <string name="llego">Car Wash Man arrived!</string>
    <string name="carwman">"Car Wash man: "</string>
    <string name="hcm">Car Wash Man</string>
    <string name="pagoprocces">Your payment is in process..</string>
    <string name="wait">wait a moment..</string>
    <string name="p1">Payment successful!</string>
    <string name="p2">Error: no payment available</string>
    <string name="p3">Error: the transaction could not be completed</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="editar_imagen_perfil">Edit Profile Picture</string>
    <string name="editar_nombre">Edit Name</string>
    <string name="editar_telefono">Edit Phone</string>
    <string name="editar_edad">Edit age</string>
    <string name="elige_opcion">Choose an option</string>
    <string name="ac_imagen">Updating Profile Image</string>
    <string name="ac_nombre">Updating Name</string>
    <string name="ac_tel">Updating Phone</string>
    <string name="ac_edad">Updating Age</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="intro">Introduce</string>
    <string name="actu">Update</string>
    <string name="actuñ">Updated</string>
    <string name="introz">Enter</string>
    <string name="camara">Camera</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="elige_ocpion">Choose an option</string>
    <string name="activa_camra">Activate the option Allow access to camera and storage</string>
    <string name="activa_permitir">Activate the option Allow storage access</string>
    <string name="img_subida">Image uploaded</string>
    <string name="img_nosubida">Image not uploaded</string>
    <string name="errorimg">An error has occurred</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="title_activity_map">Map</string>
    <string name="terminos2">Terms</string>
    <string name="c1">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="c2">\nWe welcome you to Car Wash To Go.</string>
    <string name="c3">\nThese Terms of Use govern the use of our Car Wash To Go App and include information about the Service provided, which is detailed below. When you create a Car Wash To Go account, you accept these conditions.</string>
    <string name="c41">\nCar Wash To Go our service</string>
    <string name="c4">\nWe agree to provide you with the Car Wash To Go Service, which includes the features, services, technologies, and software we offer to fulfill Car Wash To Go\'s mission: \nConnect people who want their car washed to those they want wash a car. The Service is made up of the following aspects (the Service): Opportunities at your fingertips • Opportunity to find a person close to you who is looking to have your car washed, in order to find someone who can wash it, By connecting two users through our application, practical employment opportunities are provided at any time of the day. Security • There is a rating system for those who are CarWashMan, since this way more confidence is generated in the users who surround the application. • We also have information that users provide us so the objective is to combat abuse and violations of our Conditions and policies, as well as to combat harmful and deceptive behavior. We use all the information we have, including yours, to protect our platform. In addition, we may share information about misuse or harmful content. Convenience • We have a PayPal-type payment method which helps users to receive their payments more easily and optimally, in addition to taking care of the integrity and security of each user. Conduct research and innovate. We use the information we have to study our Service and collaborate with others in research that allows us to improve it and contribute to the well-being of our community.</string>
    <string name="c5">\nPlatform Policy By using the Car Wash To Go app, you agree to this policy. \nThe term platform refers to the set of APIs, SDKs, plugins, code, specifications, documentation, technology, and services (such as content) that allow other people, including application developers and website operators, to obtain data from Car Wash To Go or provide them to us.</string>
    <string name="c6">\nGeneral conditions \n• Make sure that your application is stable and easy to navigate. For example, verify that you have successfully integrated the login. Your application should not crash during testing processes. • You must not confuse, defraud, cheat, or harass anyone. • Be transparent about your identity and that of your application. • Make sure that your device has gps since Car Wash To Go needs it. • Make sure that your device has internet since Car Wash To Go needs it. • Be sure to give the location, camera, gallery and internet permissions to our application. • Do not cache or store Instagram login credentials. • Comply with your privacy policy. • Do not cheat in the application • Maintain reliable data when registering in the application, do not use different names from yours, the application is not a game. • As an application we are not responsible for conflicts related to personal treatment of users.</string>
    <string name="c7">\nImportant information \n• An updated and 100% real email is required as it will be required to authenticate. • Some personal data is required to complete the user registration. • When creating an account you will enter our application so you must verify your account in your email, once verified, close the current session in your application and log in again, this way you are ready to use the application. • To improve your comfort and that of the users, add an image to your profile, preferably it is clear. • If any information such as your full name, age or phone has any error, it is possible to edit it in the profile section. • If you go to look for a Car Wash Man make sure to click on the button \"Search Car Wash Man\" this way the application along with the database will be looking for an available User to wash your car, if it does not appear, do not despair , Try again later. • If you find a user who will wash your car, the app will give you the distance it is located, therefore if the client is less than 100 meters away, it means that it is very close, so you can start a conversation with the Using the message button at the bottom right, this to achieve an agreement on payments, beware, the application is not responsible for the money handled in the agreements that are reached between users. • If you enter as Car Wash Man, you will see a swich which tells you at the beginning that you are disconnected, to connect basically hit the swich and with this the application will find an available user. • Once a user has been found, the “auto wash!” Button will be enabled! which adds to the PayPal button a registration both to the client and to your user, this to be able to make the payment through PayPal within our application, beware, the application is not responsible for the money handled in the agreements that are reached. between users. • In the event that a problem occurs and you can not observe both your car wash man and your client, but you have had a conversation with him, do not worry, the conversations on the main screen of our application, just that go to the chat list to meet those users with whom you have had a conversation before.</string>
    <string name="c8">\nInformation about cookies What are cookies? \nCookies are small text files that contain a string of characters that can be placed on a computer or a mobile device and serve to uniquely identify a browser or device. We may use certain technologies, such as cookies, pixels, and local storage, to provide and protect products, services, and advertisements, as well as to understand how they work. Our application uses various cookies to provide more quality of use to our customers. One of them is shown below: Third-party cookies (Google Analytics) that allow an analysis of the use of the website by its users to improve our services. Specifically, these cookies record how many times a single user visits the website, they count the number of sessions per user and store their origin. These cookies are provided as a service by Google Inc.</string>
    <string name="a1">Your email account has not been authenticated, please authenticate</string>
    <string name="a2">If you have already authenticated your account, log out and log back into your account to use the application</string>
    <string name="a3">Check Now!</string>
</resources>